(Sheldon:)Hello?
(Amy(on phone):)Sheldon, are you all right?
(Amy(on phone):)When last we spoke,
you were going to
(Amy(on phone):)take a taxi home from Raj's,
but according to Facebook,
(Amy(on phone):)you just checked in
at the Cheesecake Factory.
(Sheldon:)Yes, I was in a taxi,
(Sheldon:)but the driver
didn't look at all
(Sheldon:)like the photograph
on his license,
(Sheldon:)so I leapt out and ran for it.
(Amy:)Wise.
(Penny:)There you go.
(Penny:)Just like recovering alcoholics
drink in the Caribbean.
AMY:
Hi, bestie.
(Penny:)Oh. Hi, Amy.
(Penny:)How you been?
(Amy:)Fine.
(Amy:)From this angle,
I can see up your nose.
(Penny:)Yeah, it's a great time
to be alive, isn't it?
(Sheldon:)Don't worry.
My problems can wait
(Sheldon:)while you two hens
finish your clucking.
(Penny:)Look, Sheldon, Leonard
is dating Priya.
(Penny:)She is staying with Raj.
(Penny:)That means you're all probably
gonna be hanging out there more.
(Amy:)Penny, I'm sorry
you got dragged into this.
(Amy:)I know you're devastated
(Amy:)that your ex-boyfriend
has found an exciting new lover
(Amy:)with flawless,
caramel-colored skin.
(Penny:)Okay, I'm not upset
about Leonard and Priya.
(Amy:)Your flaring nostrils
indicate otherwise.